Guide to the Annual Reports 1973-2009 [Call #]
Eastern Connecticut State University, Publisher
- Series V - 2000-2004
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Academic Affairs: Communications (5) - Resumes, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Academic Affairs: Economics (1) - summary, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Academic Affairs: Economics (2) - Department, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - Academic Affairs: Economics (4) - Future Directions, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - Academic Affairs: Economics (5) - Resumes, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - Academic Affairs: Education (1) - summary, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - Academic Affairs: Education (2) - Department, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Academic Affairs: Education (3) - Assessment/Performance, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - Academic Affairs: Education (4) - Future Directions, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - Academic Affairs: Education (5a) - Resumes, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - Academic Affairs: Education (5b) - Resumes (cont.), 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - Academic Affairs: English (1) - summary, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - Academic Affairs: English (2) - Department, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - Academic Affairs: English (3) - Assessment/Performance, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - Academic Affairs: English (4) - Future Directions, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 85)
  - Academic Affairs: English (5) - Resumes, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 87)
  - Academic Affairs: Environmental Earth Science (2) -, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 88)
  - Academic Affairs: Environmental Earth Science (3) -, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 89)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 90)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 91)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 92)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Academic Affairs: Health and Physical Education (3) -, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Academic Affairs: Health and Physical Education (4) -, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Academic Affairs: History and Philosophy (3) -, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Academic Affairs: Learning Center, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (1) - Summary, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (2) - Office Activities and, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (4) - Access Services, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (6) - Cataloguing Department, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (7) - Curriculum Center, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (8) - Serials, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (9) - Systems, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (10) - Technical Services, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Academic Affairs: Library (11) - Templates, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Academic Affairs: Media Services, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Academic Affairs: Performing Arts, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Academic Affairs: Physical Sciences, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Academic Affairs: Psychology (1) -, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Academic Affairs: Psychology (2) -, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Academic Affairs: Psychology (3a) - Resumes, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Academic Affairs: Psychology (3b) - Resumes (cont), 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Academic Affairs: Registrar, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Academic Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Academic Affairs: Sociology (3a) - Resumes, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Academic Affairs: Sociology (3b) - Resumes (cont.), 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Academic Affairs: University Honors Programs, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Academic Affairs: Visual Arts, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Academic Affairs: Writing Program, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Administrative Affairs: Akus Gallery, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Administrative Affairs: Banner Project, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Administrative Affairs: Executive Vice President, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Administrative Affairs: Finance and Administration (1), 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Administrative Affairs: Finance and Administration (2), 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Administrative Affairs: Finance and Administration (3), 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Administrative Affairs: Finance and Administration (4), 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Administrative Affairs: Finance and Administration (5), 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Administrative Affairs: Finance and Administration (6), 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Administrative Affairs: Human Resources, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Administrative Affairs: Institute for Sustainable Energy, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Administrative Affairs: Institutional Advancement, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Administrative Affairs: Intercollegiate Athletics (1), 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Administrative Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Administrative Affairs: Office of Equity and Diversity, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Administrative Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Administrative Affairs: Student Affairs, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Administrative Affairs:, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Administrative Affairs: Student Affairs - Resumes (1), 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Administrative Affairs: Student Affairs - Resumes (2), 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Administrative Affairs: Student Affairs - Resumes (3), 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - University Relations, 2001-2002 (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - Academic: Biology - Summary; Activities; Assessment, 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - Academic: Biology - Future; Resumes, 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - Academic: Business - Summary; Activities; Assessment, 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - Academic: Business -, 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - Academic: Business - Resumes, 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - Academic: Communications -, 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - Academic: Communications - Resumes, 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - Academic: Economics -, 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 76)
  - Academic: Economics - Resumes, 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - Academic: Education - Summary; Activities, 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 78)
  - Academic: Education - Assessment; Directions, 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 79)
  - Academic: Education - Resumes, 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 80)
  - Academic: Education - Resumes, 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 81)
  - Academic: Education - Resumes, 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 82)
  - Academic: Education - Resumes, 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 83)
  - Academic: Education - News clippings, 2002-2003 (Box 12, Folder 84)
  - Academic: English - Summary; Activities; Assessment, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Academic: English - Resumes, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Academic: English - Resumes, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Academic: Honors Program, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Academic: Writing Program, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Academic: Earth Science, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Academic: Health/Physical Education -, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Academic: Health/Physical Education - Resumes, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Academic: Health/Physical Education - Resumes, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Academic: History - Activities; Assessment, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Academic: History - Resumes, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Academic: History - Resumes, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Academic: Math - Summary; Activities; Assessment, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Academic: Math - Resumes, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Academic: Modern and Classical Languages, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Academic: Performing Arts -, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Academic: Performing Arts - Resumes, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Academic: Physical Science -, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Academic: Psychology -, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Academic: Psychology - Resumes, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Academic: Sociology - Summary; Activities, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Academic: Sociology - Resumes, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Academic: Social Work, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Academic: Visual Arts -, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Academic: Visual Arts - Resumes, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Administrative: Academic Affairs, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Administrative: Arts and Sciences, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Administrative: Continuing Education, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Administrative: School of Education-, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Administrative: School of Education - Resumes, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Administrative: School of Education - Appendices, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Administrative: Advisement, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Administrative: Grants, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Administrative: Admissions, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Administrative: Educational Excellence, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Administrative: Chase Institute, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Administrative: Learning Center, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Administrative: Library -, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Administrative: Library - Resumes, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Administrative: Registrar, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Administrative: Finance, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Administrative: Card Services, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Administrative: Budget, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Administrative: Facilities, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Administrative: Public Safety, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Administrative: Planning and Institutional Advancement, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Administrative: Equity and Diversity, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Administrative: Sustainable Energy, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Administrative: ITS - Summary; Activities; Resumes, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Administrative: ITS - Resumes, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Administrative: Institutional Advancement, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Administrative: Athletics, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Academic: Biological Science, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Academic: Biological Science - Resumes, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Academic: Business, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Academic: Business - Resumes, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Academic: Communications, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Academic: Communications - Resumes, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Academic: Computer Science, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Academic: Computer Science - Resumes, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Academic: Economics, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Academic: Economics - Resumes, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Academic: Education, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Academic: Education - Resumes, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Academic: English, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Academic: English - Resumes, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Academic: Environmental Earth Science, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Academic: Environmental Earth Science - Resumes, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Academic: Health & Physical Education, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Academic: Health & Physical Education - Resumes, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Academic: History, Political Science, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Academic: History et al - Resumes, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Academic: Honors Program, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Academic: Mathematics, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Academic: Mathematics - Resumes, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Academic: Modern and Classical Languages, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Academic: Modern and Classical Languages - Resumes, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Academic: Performing Arts, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Academic: Performing Arts - Resumes., 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Academic: Physical Sciences, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Academic: Physical Sciences - Resumes, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Academic: Psychology, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Academic: Psychology - Resumes, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Academic: School of Continuing Education, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Academic: School of Continuing Education - Resumes, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Academic: Sociology, Anthropology, & Social Work, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Academic: Sociology et al - Resumes, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Academic: Social Work, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Academic: Social Work - Resumes, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Academic: Visual Arts, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Academic: Visual Arts - Resumes, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Academic: Writing Program, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Administrative: Academic Affairs, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Administrative: Academic Affairs - Resumes, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Administrative: Admissions, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Administrative: Admissions - Resumes, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Administrative: Advisement, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Administrative: Advisement - Resumes, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Administrative: Arts and Sciences, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Administrative: Arts and Sciences - Resumes, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Administrative: Auxiliary Enterprises, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Administrative: Budget Office, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Administrative: Chase Institute, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Administrative: Chase Institute - Resumes, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Administrative: Continuing Education, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Administrative: Continuing Education - Resumes, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Administrative: Educational Excellence, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Administrative: Educational Excellence - Resumes, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Administrative: Equity and Diversity, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Administrative: Executive Vice President, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - Administrative: Executive Vice President - Resumes, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - Administrative: Facilities, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Administrative: Finance and Administration, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - Administrative: Grants, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - Administrative: Grants - Resumes, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - Administrative: Information Technology Services, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 64)
  - Administrative: Information Tech Services - Resumes, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 65)
  - Administrative: Institutional Advancement, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 66)
  - Administrative: Intercollegiate Athletics, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 67)
  - Administrative: Intercollegiate Athletics - Resumes, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 68)
  - Administrative: Learning Center, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 69)
  - Administrative: Learning Center - Resumes, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 70)
  - Administrative: Library, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 71)
  - Administrative: Library - Resumes, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 72)
  - Administrative: Planning and Institutional Research, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 73)
  - Administrative: Public Safety, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 74)
  - Administrative: Registrar's Office, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 75)
  - Administrative: Registrar's Office - Resumes, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 76)
  - Administrative: School of Ed/Professional Studies, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 77)
  - Administrative: School of Education et al - Resumes, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 78)
  - Administrative: Sustainable Energy, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 79)
  - Administrative: Chase Institute, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Administrative: Chase Institute - Resumes, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Administrative: Equity and Diversity, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Administrative: Equity and Diversity - Resumes, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Administrative: Executive Vice President, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Administrative: Executive Vice President - Resumes, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Administrative: Finance, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Administrative: Finance - Resumes, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Administrative: Human Resources, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Administrative: Information Technology Services, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Administrative: Information Technology, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Administrative: Information Technology, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Administrative: Institute for Sustainable Energies, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Administrative: Institute for Sustainable, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Administrative: Institutional Advancement, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Administrative: Institutional Advancement - Resumes, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Administrative: Intercollegiate Athletics, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Administrative: Intercollegiate Athletics - Resumes, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Administrative: Learning Center, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Administrative: Learning Center - Resumes, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Administrative: Library (1), 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Administrative: Library (2), 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Administrative: Library - Resumes, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Administrative: Museum Studies, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Administrative: Planning and Institutional Research, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Administrative: Planning and Institutional, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Administrative: Registrar, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Administrative: Registrar - Resumes, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Administrative: Student Affairs - Division, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Administrative: Student Affairs - Resumes, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Administrative: Student Affairs - AOD, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Administrative: Student Affairs - Access-Ability, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Administrative: Student Affairs - Career Services, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Administrative: Student Affairs - Financial Aid, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Administrative: Student Affairs - Counseling Services, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Administrative: Student Affairs - Housing, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Administrative: Student Affairs - Health Services, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Administrative: Student Affairs - International Services, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Administrative: Student Affairs - Student Center, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Administrative: Student Affairs - Judicial Affairs, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Academic: Vice President, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Academic: Vice President - Resumes, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Academic: Dean of Arts and Sciences, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Academic: Dean of Arts and Sciences - Resumes, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Academic: School of Continuing Education, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Academic: School of Continuing Education - Resumes, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Academic: Dean of Education and Professional Studies, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Academic: Dean of Education and Professional, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Academic: Dean of Education and Professional, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Academic: Academic Advisement, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Academic: Academic Advisement - Resumes, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Academic: Academic Grants Office, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Academic: Academic Grants Office - Resumes, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Academic: Center for Educational Excellence, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Academic: Center for Educational Excellence - Resumes, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Academic: Admissions and Enrollment Management, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Academic: Admissions and Enrollment, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Academic: Biological Sciences, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Academic: Biological Sciences - Resumes, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Academic: Business, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Academic: Business - Resumes, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - Academic: Communications, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - Academic: Communications - Resumes, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - Academic: Economics and Management Services, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - Academic: Economics and Management, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - Academic: Education, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 66)
  - Academic: Education - Resumes (1), 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 67)
  - Academic: Education - Resumes (2), 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 68)
  - Academic: English, 2004- 2005 (Box 15, Folder 69)
  - Academic: English - Resumes (1), 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 70)
  - Academic: English - Resumes (2), 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 71)
  - Academic: Environmental Earth Sciences, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 72)
  - Academic: Environmental Earth Sciences - Resumes, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 73)
  - Academic: Health and Physical Education, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 74)
  - Academic: Health and Physical Education - Resumes, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 75)
  - Academic: History, Political Science, and Philosophy, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 76)
  - Academic: History, Political Science, and, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 77)
  - Academic: History, Political Science, and, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 78)
  - Academic: Honors Program, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 79)
  - Academic: Honors Program - Resumes, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 80)
  - Academic: Mathematics/Computer Science, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 81)
  - Academic: Mathematics/Computer Science - Resumes, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 82)
  - Academic: Modern and Classical Languages, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 83)
  - Academic: Modern and Classical Languages - Resumes, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 84)
  - Academic: Performing Arts, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 85)
  - Academic: Performing Arts - Resumes, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 86)
  - Academic: Physical Sciences, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 87)
  - Academic: Physical Sciences, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 88)
  - Academic: Psychology, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 89)
  - Academic: Psychology - Resumes (1), 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 90)
  - Academic: Psychology - Resumes (2), 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 91)
  - Academic: Social Work, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 92)
  - Academic: Social Work - Resumes, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 93)
  - Academic: Sociology, Anthropology, and Social Work, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 94)